ROBERTO MEJIA

Denver, NC 28037 704-906-0722 Rmeji2@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

I have the ability to respond and resolve customer's requests and concerns promptly. Have experience in quoting and writing new policies like Auto, home and renters. I work in customer service setting helping customer resolve issues and informing them depending on the circumstances, also licensed in property and casualty in all 50 states.

EXPERIENCE

2023- PRESENT

BILINGUAL PROPERTY AND LIABILITY SPECIALIST CONCENTRIX, Charlotte, NC

- Concentrix is a third party employed by Allstate with employees keeping the same role.
- As insurance rates increase, we have to be able to provide customer with a brief description of the reason of change.
- Review customers policies to help find discounts or ways to save customers on premiums.

2019-2022

BILINGUAL PROPERTY AND LIABILITY SPECIALIST

ALLSTATE, Charlotte, NC

- Add and remove vehicle and drivers and verified required information per state guideline.
- Helped changed addresses or move policy to requested state.
- Inform customers of missing documents required by insurance.

BILINGUAL DRIVEWISE/ MILEWISE SPECIALIST (PILOT)

- Identify and report app issues & what phone versions were being affected.
- Informing customer about discount and reward their eligibility.
- Enrolling and unenrolling Drive wise drivers per request.
- Walking customer thru installation process & informing how to use the app.

2016-2018

Advance painting

Charlotte, NC

- Painted and renovated house promptly and as needed.
- Oversaw placement of orders for products at retail locations.
- Operated lifts for painting and repairing purposes.
- Drove commercial vehicles for delivery of products and workers.

2015-2016

IQOR Health Insurance customer service

Charlotte, NC

- Helped customers update records in database, process payments & assisted with problem resolution.
- Instructed in HIPPA laws also worked in a fast-paced call center environment.
- Informed customers of healthcare benefits and impacts it would have.
- Helped connect customers with healthcare assistance if needed.

ROBERTO MEJIA

Denver, NC 28037 704-906-0722 Rmeji2@gmail.com

SKILLS

- Clear communication skills
- Ability to work under pressure
- Adaptability to change

- Experienced in health insurance
- Advanced computer skills
- Fluent in Spanish and English

LICENSES

- Insurance Producer
 - o Property
 - o Casualty

EDUCATION

Central Piedmont Community College, Charlotte NC

Associates in arts, 2013 GPA 2.8

University of North Carolina at Charlotte, Charlotte NC

Full stack coding, 2023 in progress

PROFFESSIONAL REFRENCES

JOEY RIOS ALLSTATE SALES DEPT 7875489807 PREVIOUS SUPERVISOR

DIANA RIVERA REMODELING BUISNESS OWNER 9802485073 PREVIOUS SUPERVISOR

GIEZI BERMUDEZ DUKE ENERGY, BUISNESS DEPT. 9802281495 PREVOIUS CO WORKER

SANDRA SOLANO SNYDERS LANCE, MANAGER 7044495132